[theme music playing]
-Careful.
-Hey!
[Arnaldo] I don't like what
you did earlier.
[Diego] If you always
got what you wanted back then,
it won't happen this time.
Ivy doesn't like you.
-[Ivy screams]
-Oh!
[Ivy] What were you doing?!
-How dare you peep on me!
-I said I'm sorry!
[Loring] He had only one best friend,
and she was his one and only true love.
What's her name, Diego?
Lily. Her name is Lily.
I have here an old draft,
the deed of donation from 1958,
confirming that the land
was donated to the farmers.
[crowd clamoring]
So, you got what you wanted.
When do I get my end of the bargain?
Miss Ivy was concerned.
All right, Nanny. I'll talk to Miss Aguas.
You're different.
You've got the perfect
characteristics of a first lady.
My first lady.
[Diego] Miss Aguas, wait!
How dare you go against your own family?
If you pull this stunt again,
Diego, you will answer to me.
You will answer to me!
[Raul] Someday I'll be
as powerful as them.
And when that happens, I'll leave Emilia.
And I'll choose you, Camia.
[Carlotta] Diego is a good man.
You're fighting for the same thing.
It isn't wrong to open
your heart to someone.
I shouldn't feel this way about
you because you're the enemy.
But why can't I get you off my mind?
[Ivy] Joan, how are the contracts?
-Okay, very good.
-Ivy.
Ivy, where are you going?
I have to go to Manila
to meet with a new investor.
Why don't you rest first?
I know you're stressed out
with everything that's happening here.
Thank you for your concern,
but I can handle myself.
You know I have to attend to my business.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Please take care.
What happened?
I'll go check, ma'am.
Joan, did we run out of working vans?
I'm sorry, Miss Ivy.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
[Diego] Sir, what happened?
We have a flat tire, sir.
Let me help you.
That's the flat tire, sir.
I think you drove over a nail.
Do you have tools with you?
-Yes, sir.
-Can you go get them, please?
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary
continues playing]
Mr. Torillo.
Miss Aguas, so this is your car.
Yes. It's a company car.
I'm going back to Manila
for a business meeting.
Thank you for letting us
hold the dialogue.
I was supposed to tell you that
when I saw you with Arnaldo.
Sorry for ruining your moment.
Nothing's going on
between your brother and I.
I mean, Mr. Mayor.
I'll just help your driver.
-Mr. Torillo.
-Sir.
Thank you.
Even though we're on different sides…
you're still willing to help me out.
Also, I'm thankful…
that you aren't forcing me
out of this town.
Maybe…
it's time we called a truce between us.
Since you're helping me…
maybe this can be
the start of our friendship.
Okay, Miss Aguas.
You can call me Ivy.
Diego.
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
I've got to hand it to you Ardientes.
Your charity events are always successful.
Of course, Senator.
This is the reason we're
so close to our constituents.
By the way, where is Raul?
[chuckles softly]
He's taking care of something
for our business.
By the way, our EPZ project
starts next week.
Okay.
But I heard your son, Diego,
tried to stop the project.
Sorry to say, but if you can't
control your son,
what more the people of Ardiente?
Oh, I think we have a
very interesting guest
behind you, Emilia.
-Hi, Senator.
-Raul.
Hello.
Emilia, I'm sorry I'm late.
For you.
What a pleasant surprise.
Well, shall we have something to eat?
Thank you.
Miss Aguas.
-Ivy.
-[both chuckle]
Thank you, Diego.
Sorry it's not much. But it tastes good.
[mellow music plays]
This is your favorite, huh?
How did you know?
Well, Miss Loring sells these, right?
Yes, ever since I was a kid.
It's my best friend's favorite, too.
Your best friend,
she's the one
we talked about before, right?
The one who helped you lose weight
because you were chubby…
[snickers]
…back then.
That wasn't the only thing she taught me.
She also taught me how
to stand up for myself,
to know my worth.
You know…
I tried looking for her…
but couldn't find her.
Sometimes, I think about how she's doing.
I wonder what she looks like.
I don't even know if she's alive.
I don't know why she just disappeared.
She never came back.
Diego.
Yeah?
Diego, that girl…
[Joan] Ma'am!
Miss Ivy, the car's ready now.
We can go now.
Let's go.
Hurry up, please.
I'll just take this with me, Diego.
I really have to go.
Make sure you eat it, okay?
Take care, Ivy. Be safe!
Take care, sir.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
[engine turns over]
Emilia, wait.
Emilia.
What's wrong with you?
How many times do you have to lie?
I'm so tired of it.
How many families do I have to kill?
We celebrate that day only once a year,
when I remember that you loved me once,
but you still can't give me that.
Looks like you failed
to impress Senator, Mom.
You know, this is all your fault.
If you didn't force me to have a dialogue
with those wretched farmers,
they wouldn't see any flaws
with my project.
Well, I think Ivy has a point.
We should befriend the people,
not push them away.
How do you expect me to trust your plans,
when all you really want
is to get inside Ivy's pants?
You know what?
You're stupid.
I'm stupid? Really?
Why don't you look at yourself?
Until now, you're being stupid for Dad…
who doesn't even know
what's happening here.
Just like your other good-for-nothing son.
You know, I can't help but think
that if Grandpa were here…
he wouldn't let this slide.
We wouldn't be having these problems.
Well, I'm the one here.
And I'm more than capable
of solving these problems.
Good morning.
Is Mr. Fernan there?
Is he the leader of the cooperative?
We have to talk to him.
[tense music playing]
Mom.
What did you do?
Arnaldo, I don't want any stress.
So, I did what I had to do.
I taught them a lesson.
[phone rings]
Jepoy.
What?! I'll be there.
Mister, take me to the cooperative. Hurry.
Why is this happening?
The governor promised
that she wouldn't evict us
from this land anymore.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
And is this even legal?
Do you have papers?
Are you police officers?
The word of the Ardientes is the law here.
Our job is to implement them,
even if it means
evicting you from this land.
If you don't give us a hard time,
then no one will get hurt.
But if you do,
then you'll be sorry.
-That's not what we agreed on.
-No!
-Come on, let's talk this out.
-We won't leave.
You'll have to kill us first
before you can throw us out.
-Where are you going?
-Where else?
I'll handle it.
I'm the head of this project.
Okay, I'm sure our private army
needs all the help they can get.
Just be careful.
You know you'll be evicting a
lot of farmers from that place.
And make sure that
after everything is over,
I'll never see their faces again.
You take care, okay?
Who's that?
-[tense music plays]
-It's Miss Aguas.
Diego.
Diego, it's Miss Ivy.
What's she doing here?
She's showing her true colors.
[Pandoy] But I thought--
We were wrong about her.
She just tricked us.
What's happening here?
Ma'am, the governor wants them to leave.
Don't tell me you didn't know.
Diego, I didn't!
Believe it or not, I didn't know.
Miss Ivy, the governor
wants us out of this place.
-Yeah.
-That's true.
What?!
Diego.
[tense music intensifies]
-She's evicting you?
-Yes.
-Ivy.
-Diego.
Mr. Mayor, it didn't have to come to this.
Why is this happening?
You can't plead their case anymore, Ivy.
They have to leave,
whether you like it or not.
No. Do something about it.
Diego, there's nothing we can do.
No, Nanny.
As long as we're alive, we'll fight back.
That's right!
-Let's go, Nanny.
-We're going to fight!
Everyone, let's band together!
Let's go, everyone.
You will never have this land!
-This land is ours!
-You can't make us leave!
-We're going to fight!
-You won't take this from us!
[indistinct shouting]
We will not leave!
-Get out of here!
-We're going to fight!
Arnaldo, do something.
[indistinct shouting]
This land is ours!
Miss Aguas, let's go.
[indistinct shouting]
Come on!
-Mr. Mayor.
-Let them be.
Do something. Make them stop.
Go on. Make them disperse.
Butchoy!
Let's go. Let's go.
Butchoy.
-Wait!
-Miss Aguas!
-Butchoy!
-Butchoy.
-Stop!
Don't cry, Butchoy.
Mr. Mayor, make them stop!
There's an innocent child here!
[tense music playing]
Miss Aguas, you should get out of here.
You need to go!
Take Butchoy and go!
Madrigal, go get her. Make it quick.
-You need to go.
-Make them disperse.
-You have to leave. Go.
-Calm down! Pandoy!
-Hey! Hey!
-Stop!
[Ivy] Don't cry, Butchoy. Don't cry.
-Let's go
-But the kid--
-Let's go!
-Butchoy!
[clamoring]
Hold on! Stop!
Hey, get your hands off them!
-Pandoy!
-Stop it!
-Wait!
-Let's go.
Mr. Mayor, have pity on your brother.
Hey! Stop! Wait!
[Diego] I said let her go!
There's nothing we can do. He wanted that.
Wait! Wait!
[Loring screams]
[tense music continues playing]
-Let her go! Wait!
-[Loring] Diego!
Stop!
-Get in!
-Let them go!
Arnaldo! Make them stop! Wait!
-[Loring] Diego!
-Stop!
Ouch!
Bastards!
Stop!
-Close the door!
-[Loring] Diego!
Hold on. Hold on.
Stop! This is wrong!
-Come on. Go.
-Diego!
-[man] Diego!
-Hold on!
Get out of here!
Mayor! Mayor!
Now what, Diego?
Are you going to punch me?
Then do it!
Hit me!
You don't have it in you.
[screams]
Why did it have to be like this?!
Tell me, Arnaldo!
Why can't you all understand?!
This is for everyone!
This is for the town!
Lies!
You know that's a lie!
It hasn't been 30 days
since you gave us the notice!
You don't have a court order,
because we all know
this didn't go through due process.
The farmers will file an appeal!
And while the Supreme Court
hasn't made its final decision,
then you can't force us off this land.
You can't kick the farmers out!
[tense music intensifies]
Well?! Say something!
What now?!
Release him.
Break it off, everyone.
All right. Let them go.
But remember this.
We wouldn't have resorted to violence
if it weren't for your stubbornness!
Everything that happened today
is your fault!
It's your fault.
[camera clicks]
Let's go.
-Move!
-Diego!
-Wait!
-Stop! Arnaldo!
-Diego!
-Arnaldo!
-Move out!
-Nanny!
-Diego!
-Let's move!
-[engine revs]
-Diego!
Raul! Aren't you going out?
When I'm not here, you get mad.
And now that I'm here,
you tell me to leave!
I'm not leaving because I'm
waiting for your son, Arnaldo!
Yes? I heard my name.
Arnaldo, what did you do?
Why did you let Diego get beaten up?
-Diego? Well, he asked for it.
-He asked for it?
This is your brother we're talking about.
Raul, can you calm down?
I allowed that to happen
to teach him a lesson.
It's not as if his life was in any danger.
What kind of answer is that, Emilia?
You let them hurt Diego?
What kind of family is this?
We're not done yet, Arnaldo.
Oh, Ivy, I'm sorry
you had to witness that.
My husband isn't politically savvy,
so I wasn't able to teach him any manners.
I guess that's why I was
so patient with those farmers.
You know, we live in a house
full of parasites.
But you're not included, Arnaldo.
Anyway, the operation stopped
because of what happened.
But once we demolish the houses,
they won't have any choice but
to live in the relocation site.
I have to go to my office. Excuse me.
Will the project still push through?
Yes, of course.
We're Ardientes. We get what we want.
You can't do this to us.
We're just fighting for our rights!
-Ramon, calm down!
-He's right.
I can't trust those Ardientes anymore.
Especially after treating us
like animals today!
Let's talk about this peacefully.
We're all residents of Ardiente…
so, please, just give us
a little consideration.
Don't tell us that.
Tell that to the mayor,
or maybe, the governor,
or maybe, Miss Ivy Aguas.
[tense music plays]
Actually, that's what I wanted
to make sure of.
Emilia, is this what you really want?
For the people you govern
to lose their homes and their livelihood?
This isn't right.
Okay, sure.
You'll relocate them elsewhere.
But that's far from the life they know.
Emilia, have you thought of that?
I thought Miss Ivy asked them to stop.
She looked so surprised
when she saw what was happening.
[Loring] I'm so confused.
Is she telling the truth or not?
Fine, I want to invest here
and partner up with you,
but, Emilia, this is not what I wanted.
[sighs]
Ivy, you know, you surprised me.
You know what? We should celebrate.
I brought out my most expensive
bottle of wine.
[sighs]
Victory is sweet when
you get what you want.
But it is sweeter…
if you get it without hurting anyone.
Emilia, you even let your son get hurt.
He went against me.
He went against us.
That's why I had to do that.
Otherwise, your investment
would go down the drain.
And I don't want that to happen.
Hmm… Unless you've switched sides.
[tense music intensifies]
Excuse me.
[Jepoy] What's his name?
The governor's really scary.
Imagine that?
She kicked those farmers off their land.
Well, the governor already
told them to move ahead of time.
It's those farmers' fault.
They overstayed their welcome.
What the Ardientes did was right.
I guess.
But what if those farmers
get back at them?
That's impossible.
As if they'd have the guts to do that.
Thing is, no matter
how obedient sheep may be,
when their patience runs out,
they can turn into wolves.
They might come for the Ardientes…
or even their investor, Ivy Aguas.
That's going to make our jobs
as bodyguards harder.
That's more work for us.
What do you think, Jepoy?
Farmers? You think they stand
a chance against us?
Drink your coffee.
-You're just hungry.
-[phone vibrates]
MEET ME AT THE PARKING LOT
Anyway, see you guys later.
Sure.
[phone rings]
Ivy?
Jepoy, I want you to check on Diego.
Make sure he's all right.
Diego?
Yes, check on Diego,
Miss Loring and Mr. Pandoy.
Everyone at the cooperative.
I want you to make sure they're okay.
Jepoy, I can't leave
because I'm with Emilia.
I know she's getting suspicious.
She's starting to doubt me.
So, please, do this for me.
Okay?
Ivy?
What are you doing here?
I had to take a call.
I know, I heard.
Who were you talking to?
I was talking to Nanny Carlotta.
I just gave her some instructions.
Why?
Is there anything you wanna talk about?
Are you following me, Emilia?
No!
You just look agitated.
And I'm sure you've heard
about the dispersal.
I just wanna make sure
that it's business as usual.
That it's still on.
Isn't that Mr. Diego Ardiente?
[tires screech]
Mr. Diego, what's the problem?
Let them go!
Aren't you scared, Mr. Diego?
We're armed.
-And you know…
-Hey, look, it's Diego!
…we can't follow your orders.
Why, is the governor here? Or the mayor?
You're my family's private army.
And I'm an Ardiente!
-Let's get down.
-Come on.
-Dad! Dad!
-Hey!
-Hey, Loring.
-Diego, Diego.
Hey, who said you could get down?
-Hey!
-Let me go!
Diego!
You have no right to hurt them!
We'll see!
-Hold on!
-Please! Don't!
Go on, shoot! Shoot me!
Come on! Shoot me!
Say goodbye to your protectors
if something bad happens to me!
I know you're just following orders…
but that's no reason
to act like criminals!
Everyone!
-Yeah?
-Come with me.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-All right, Diego.
-Nanny, Uncle, let's go.
-Thank you, Diego.
-Dad! Dad!
Dad!
[people clamoring]
[Emilia] No, no, no.
Why was the press there?
Now, I have to clean it up.
News blackout.
These rookies do nothing
but mess things up.
Who am I?
Cinderella who has to mop up their mess?
I'm lucky I'm good at it.
[Loring] Oh, my goodness.
What happened here?
They really won't stop.
They'll do everything to make us give up.
So, everyone…
we have to be strong and brave.
Let's show them that whatever
happens, we stand united.
-Diego.
-Careful.
Dad.
[Ivy] Jepoy.
Jepoy, what's the update on Diego?
I passed by the co-op.
I saw Diego and the farmers there.
You did?
Jepoy, thank you.
That's good to know.
Ivy.
I just want to ask something.
What's going on between--
Forget it. Never mind.
Anyway, take care, okay?
And thanks again.
You really love everyone here, don't you?
I do, Dad.
They're like family to me.
But that's not the reason
I'm helping them.
Dad, they're in the right.
If no one will stand up for them,
all this injustice won't stop.
I know. But I also want to remind you
that you're not just dealing
with random people.
You're dealing with your mom and brother.
I know, Dad. But nothing will change
if no one stands up for what's right.
Son, I'm proud of you.
Because you didn't
listen to all the things
your grandfather
and mother have been spouting.
Instead, you chose to believe in yourself.
It's good that you're true
to your own principles.
I just hope one day, I can do the same.
I want to be like you.
I want to be brave
and stand up for myself.
-Ma'am, good morning.
-Let me get that.
Okay, ma'am.
Ivy.
Isn't that too much?
To be honest, this
isn't even enough to pay
for all the pain I've caused.
Nowhere near enough.
But how will you give it to them?
Through Diego.
I'll tell him that it's just
a small amount
to help the people in
the cooperative start over.
Ivy, how about Emilia?
What if she finds out you're doing this?
Don't worry about Emilia.
Let me handle it.
What's important is we help.
Look.
[tense music playing]
Good morning.
Have some breakfast.
The weather's nice today,
just like your mood.
Of course! Why wouldn't I be?
I've fixed all our problems.
Except for one small thing.
You.
Do you think I forgot what you did to me?
You didn't come home for our anniversary.
You know what? Starting today,
you're not allowed to go out.
And you'll stop that business of yours.
You can only go out
if my men will accompany you.
You'll be with me, 24/7.
Wait, what is this?
Am I in high school again?
Are you grounding me? Is that it?
That, or I'll have you arrested
for what you did to Papa.
You decide.
[tense music playing]
A story still came out.
Fine. But you better be ready
for what I'll do next.
Just sit here, okay?
I'll just get the clothes
I left outside to dry.
Stay there.
[pensive music plays]
Jasmin.
Jasmin?
Diego.
Ivy, what are you doing here?
How are you?
I mean, how's everyone?
I just want to know if you're
all okay after what happened.
Uh…
Diego.
What's this for?
I want to help all the people here.
So the cooperative can start over.
Thank you, Ivy, but…
we can't accept this.
No, Diego. Please.
Please, accept it.
-I just want to help.
-No, we can't accept this.
I just--
I know this is the only way
you can help us now.
And I don't hold it against you.
It's easy to trade dignity for money.
But money has always made things
worse for the people here.
Their dignity and principles
are all they have left…
and those are the things we'll
hold onto until the very end.
[tense music playing]
Looks like you're only waiting
for the party's endorsement
to push through with
your senatorial bid, Emilia.
Talk is cheap, Senator.
So, when are we going to make it official?
Well, at last,
you had the guts to evict those farmers.
That shows your strong conviction,
and I assume you'll fix
your problems with your son.
I'll fix it all, Senator.
For as long as you continue to endorse me.
And I promise to give it my best.
I won't disappoint you, or the party.
Shall we?
[townsfolk chanting] We will
fight for our land rights!
We will fight for our land rights!
You can't do that here, sir.
We don't want any trouble.
[man] We just want to talk
to the governor.
Governor, they've been there all day.
[man] We'll just talk to her.
[guard] They don't want to leave.
[man] We'll fight for our…
-Should we make them leave?
-No, no, no, no.
[townsfolk] Fight for our land rights!
A good leader knows how
to handle her detractors.
I'll face them. I'll fix this.
-All right, ma'am.
-Fight for our rights!
Mr. Fernan, the governor.
[townsfolk chanting]
We'll fight for our land!
-Fight!
-For our land!
We will fight for our land rights!
Governor, good afternoon.
Mr. Fernan, Mr. Ramon,
what brings you here?
Drop the act, Governor.
We're here to fight for our land!
[townsfolk] That's right!
Mr. Ramon, we politicians know
what's best for you citizens.
But was it right to lock us up?
To have us arrested?!
To have your son beaten up?!
-That's right!
Mr. Ramon, aren't you
Mr. Fernan's right-hand man?
When the EPZ project begins,
I'll make you the head.
We don't need that!
What we need
is the ownership of that land!
-That's right!
-If you don't give it back,
I will bring this issue to
your political enemies myself!
-What?
-So that no Ardiente will win
-in the next election!
-That's right!
We have the right to go
against the Ardientes!
Our rights against the Ardientes!
Freedom from the Ardientes!
We will fight for our land rights!
[tense music playing]
-You!
-[Emilia cries]
You and your weaknesses as a woman!
-You never think, do you?
-Ouch!
A woman like you, getting
herself drunk senseless?!
-Have some dignity!
-Ouch!
Ouch!
I don't want you to be involved
in any of this anymore.
Emilia, you disappoint me.
-I meant--
-Shut up.
Let the men handle this.
A woman like you wouldn't
understand anything.
There are things about your credentials
which we find lacking.
If you can't reach Julio's
level of influence,
you'll only be wasting time and money.
Because you'll surely lose.
I'll fix it all, Senator.
For as long as you continue to endorse me.
And I promise to give it my best.
I won't disappoint you, or the party.
What we need is the ownership
of that land!
If you won't give it to us,
I will bring this issue…
to your political enemies myself!
-What?
-So that no Ardiente…
-will win in the next election!
-That's right!
[tense music intensifies]
[line ringing]
Hello.
[tense music playing]
-There.
-I warned you, Ramon.
You shouldn't have argued
with the governor like that!
You know how Mr. Ramon is, Dad.
He blows up once he's fed up.
I used to fight for the Ardientes
and defended them
against their detractors.
Oh, come on.
But this time, they've crossed the line!
What's your plan, Mr. Ramon?
Are you pushing through with your threat?
If the governor won't stop
trying to steal our land.
Okay. That's enough.
Let's just finish this.
-Jack.
-Yes?
-Isn't that ready yet?
-Everything's all tapped.
-But still no power.
-Good grief.
Just a bit more, and we'll be done here.
All right then.
I'll go check the power lines.
I think I saw
a loose cable there last night.
-All right.
-You stay here.
All right. Take care, okay?
Wrap that around there. Right there.
It might fall over.
Where's Loring?
I'm getting hungry.
[ominous music playing]
I heard the news.
I must admit, I'm surprised
you could do that.
I'm surprised you could do that to me.
You had me beaten up by your private army.
I know we disagree
on a lot of things, but…
but I can't believe
that just because of this…
you turned your back on your own brother.
You can't quit being stupid, can you?
Why don't you tell yourself
the same thing?
You're the one who turned
your back on this family!
Don't you dare think that
I'll just let this slide.
I'm not the kid you used to make fun of.
Whatever you do to me…
I can do to you, too.
[tense music playing]
-It's delicious.
-Here you go.
Can I have some?
-Where's Ramon?
-Me, too.
Hold on.
Ramon's not here yet.
Nimfa, why don't you bring him some?
-Hey, save some for me.
-We will. Don't worry.
-We'll save you some.
-We can't finish all of this.
[Nimfa] Mr. Ramon!
Time to eat! Miss Loring
prepared some food for us.
Mr. Ramon?
[ominous music playing]
Mr. Ramon!
Help!
Please, help me!
[muffled] Help! Help--
Mister, help us!
[tense music playing]
Mister.
[gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[Diego] Hey, everyone!
-Let's eat up!
-[cheering]
Oh, my. What did you bring?
-Noodles, Nanny.
-Oh, wow.
You just had to compete
with me, didn't you?
-Let me get that for you.
-Nanny…
your cooking is still
the best here in the whole town.
-Isn't that right, everyone?
-That's right!
-Long live Loring!
-This is still the best.
Oh, really now? All right.
Let's open this up.
Let's dig in!
Looks good!
[Loring] What do you want?
-Let's eat!
-I want some.
What?
[Dolfo] It's so sad to think…
our days here at the co-op are numbered.
Come on, Rodolfo, don't think like that.
Especially now that your son,
Ramon, and Fernan
have joined forces,
we're stronger than ever!
-Really?
-That's right.
And while we live, there's hope.
-I agree.
All we have to do is to fight fair.
-Correct.
-That's right.
Just like Diego here.
Diego, thank you for standing up for us.
You're so kind and brave.
-[man] You're our idol.
-Of course, Nanny.
Just keep giving me fritters,
and I'll be fine.
-Wow.
-Here's the noodles.
-Time for the noodles.
-Noodles for long life.
I brought a lot of noodles.
-Nimfa! Over here!
-[Nimfa cries]
-[Loring] This is for long life.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Nimfa.
-Hey, Nimfa. Are you okay?
[Loring] What happened?
Mr. Dolfo.
-What is it?
-It's…
it's about Mr. Ramon.
What happened to my son?
Where's Ramon? What happened to him?
-Hey.
-Nimfa.
Nimfa, what happened to Mr. Ramon?
Nimfa.
Mr. Ramon got into an accident.
-What happened?
-Mr. Dolfo.
-Ramon, my son!
-[townsfolk crying]
[man] What happened to Ramon?
Ramon! My son!
-Mr. Dolfo.
-Dolfo.
- Ramon, my son!
-Dolfo. Dolfo.
[Loring] Why Ramon?
He was still so young.
Why did this happen to him?
Why is this happening to us?
If that's what Ramon's fate is--
[Diego] Uncle Pandoy's right.
It was an accident.
No, Diego.
This wasn't an accident.
I saw someone following Mr. Ramon…
but when I got there, he ran off.
This wasn't an accident.
Are you saying somebody killed
Mister Ramon?
-Governor.
-Yes? What's the problem?
Nothing big, Governor.
If they're not suspecting anything
after I had Ramon killed,
then why do we have to talk?
The thing is, Governor…
Mr. Fernan's daughter saw me.
What?!
Do you think this is connected
to Ramon's threat against the governor?
What do you mean, Mr. Dolfo?
But I'm sure she didn't recognize me.
Well, we can't do anything
about the mess you made.
But it's good that happened.
So they start to realize
that they shouldn't be going
against the Ardientes.
[dramatic music playing]
[screams]
[Arnaldo] You always make decisions
without thinking of the consequences.
[Emilia] You think you're better than me?
I wish I wasn't born an Ardiente!
[Ivy] I'm really sorry.
I just came here to offer my condolences
and tell you that the project is on hold.
Did someone have to die first
before you realized
what you're doing is wrong?
[Jepoy] Mayor, I heard Miss
Aguas was going to the co-op.
Why would she go there?
She knows the farmers
have a rift with the Ardientes!
-Ivy, wait.
-You're concerned?
Do you think I'd ever let you get hurt?
[theme music plays]